<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on A minimal Hugo website</title>
    <link>/website/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on A minimal Hugo website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Co-Enriching Microflora Associated with Culture Based Methods to Detect Salmonella from Tomato Phyllosphere</title>
      <link>/website/meetings/2017-07-28-ottesen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/website/meetings/2017-07-28-ottesen/</guid>
      <description>Andrea R. Ottesen, Antonio Gonzalez, Rebecca Bell, Caroline Arce, Steven Rideout, Marc Allard, Peter Evans, Errol Strain, Steven Musser, Rob Knight, Eric Brown, James B. Pettengill Link: http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0073079
When: Friday, July 28 at 10:00AM
Where: MIAEH conference room (SPH 2242CC)
Abstract The ability to detect a specific organism from a complex environment is vitally important to many fields of public health, including food safety. For example, tomatoes have been implicated numerous times as vehicles of foodborne outbreaks due to strains of Salmonella but few studies have ever recovered Salmonella from a tomato phyllosphere environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Folks on the club mailing list</title>
      <link>/website/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/website/people/</guid>
      <description> Sarah Allard (sallard@umd.edu) Justine Beaulieu Brian Brubach Anthony Bui Mary Callahan Victoria Cepeda Suhana Chattopadhyay Jess Chopyk (jchopyk@umd.edu) Hillary Craddock Angela Ferelli Jay Ghurye Lydia Ingabire Prachi Kulkarni Govindaraj Kumar Xingchen Liu Leena Malayil Shirley Micallef Rianna Murray Dan Nasko (dnasko@umiacs.umd.edu) Mansi Panse Mihai Pop Greg Raspanti Shamar Rundhawa Amy Sapkota Nidhi Shah Eoghen Smyth Sultana Solaiman Todd Treagen  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helpful resources for your research</title>
      <link>/website/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/website/resources/</guid>
      <description>Yeah, I&amp;rsquo;ll get around to putting this together&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>